

Gabriele Napoli

Developer 26 y.o. https://gabrielenapoli.dev

Email gabriele.nap@gmail.com

Website gabrielenapoli.dev

Github @gNaps

Linkedin@gabriele-napolia87529185

I am a web developer and I love to design and create applications and products. Right now I'm working as a frontend developer but in the past I also had experience as a backend developer. I'm very interested in javascript and working with technologies like Angular, React and NodeJS.

Experiences

Frontend Developer @ Kalpa

2021 - current

Management of the entire work pipeline for the development of frontend applications in the IoT world. Estimates, evelopment and testing. Starting projects by installing the appropriate libraries and configuring environments.

Used technologies: Angular 12+, Docker, Git, AWS cloud.

Fullstack Developer @ SB Italia

2018 - 2021

Design and development of ERP and CRM applications. R&D to improve the stack and optimise legacy applications. Development of the entire stack: frontend, backend and database. Deploy in production and on mobile stores.

Used technologies: jQuery, AngularJs, C#, MSSQL, Ionic.

Skills

Javascript Typescript Angular

React NodeJS SQL CSS HTML

Education

2015-2019

Laurea Triennale Informatica, UNIMIB

2015

Liceo Scientifico Ettore Conti, MI